Guide to the New York University Archives Biographical Files MC.317
New York University Archives
New York University Archives Biographical Files
Undated
New York University Archives
MC.317
96 Linear Feet in 192 manuscript boxes
The New York University Archives Biographical Files consist of files containing biographical material on people connected with New York University or are notable for other reasons. The collection was created by the University Archives to make a central collection for reference staff fulfilling requests for information on individuals associated with the University. Materials date from the late 19th century through the early 21st century.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Some materials in this collection were transferred from various New York University departments in 2016 and 2017. No information was recorded about the acquisition of the other materials in this collection. The accession numbers associated with these transfers include 2016.041 and 2017.036.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in alphabetical order by last name.
Historical note
The New York University Archives Biographical Files was created by the University Archives to make a central collection for reference staff fulfilling requests for information on individuals associated with the University.
Custodial History
In May 2025, biographical materials were transferred from the New York University Archives Portrait Files (MC 319). The accession number associated with this accretion is 2025.025.
Scope and Contents
The New York University Archives Biographical Files consist of files containing biographical material on New York University (NYU) professors or people who are connected with NYU in another way. The files contain clippings, programs, curricula vitae, memorandum, booklets, business cards, notes, correspondence, and biographical information forms collected by the Office of Public Affairs. Materials date from the late 19th century through the early 21st century.
Appraisal
In May 2025, materials related to Joseph Smalley were removed and placed into the Matthew Wise Collection on the Joseph Smalley AIDS Memorial Quilt Panel (MC 422).
Biographical files.; Clippings files.
- Aaronson, Doris R., undated (Box 1)
- Abbe, Richard F., undated (Box 1)
- Abbott, Austin, undated (Box 1)
- Abbott, Lyman, undated (Box 1)
- Abdullah, Dr. Abdul J. (FAS), undated (Box 1)
- Abeles, Sophia, undated (Box 1)
- Abele, Manlio O., undated (Box 1)
- Abrams, Charles (LAW), undated (Box 1)
- Abelles, Joseph C., undated (Box 1)
- Abelson, Raziel A., undated (Box 1)
- Aberth, William (FAS), undated (Box 1)
- Abraham, Dr. Williams I. (GSAS), undated (Box 1)
- Abrahams, Paul W. (GSAS), undated (Box 1)
- Abrams, George J., undated (Box 1)
- Abrams, Jane, undated (Box 1)
- Abrams, Joan D., undated (Box 1)
- Abrams, Dr. Raymond M. (MED), undated (Box 1)
- Abrams, Robert, undated (Box 1)
- Abu-Lughod, Lila, undated (Box 1)
- Ackerman, Mona, undated (Box 1)
- Ackerman, Bernard (MED), undated (Box 1)
- Ackerman, S.B., undated (Box 1)
- Ackerman, Simona Riklis, undated (Box 1)
- Ackley, Sheldon (ADMIN), undated (Box 1)
- Acton, Sir Harold, undated (Box 1)
- Adam, Sister Alice Mae, undated (Box 1)
- Adamiak, Theodore J., undated (Box 1)
- Adams, Herbert William, undated (Box 1)
- Adams, James Truslow, undated (Box 1)
- Adams, John V. (SEHNAP), undated (Box 1)
- Adams, Mark H., undated (Box 1)
- Adams, Sherman (STERN), undated (Box 1)
- Adams, Stanley, undated (Box 1)
- Adam, Thomas R. (FAS), undated (Box 1)
- Addams, Jane, undated (Box 1)
- Addelston, Harold K., undated (Box 1)
- Addelston, Herbert, undated (Box 1)
- Adelman, Joseph A., undated (Box 1)
- Adelson, Judah, undated (Box 1)
- Adisman, Dr. I Kenneth (DENTAL), undated (Box 1)
- Adkins, Nelson (1897-1976), undated (Box 1)
- Adler, Alexandra (Medical School), undated (Box 1)
- Adler, Alexis, undated (Box 1)
- Adler, Claire Fisher (FAS), undated (Box 1)
- Adler, Claudio Lomnitz, undated (Box 1)
- Adler, Edward J., undated (Box 1)
- Adler, George J., undated (Box 1)
- Adler, Leona K. (FAS), undated (Box 1)
- Adler, Rita (BS - Nutrition), undated (Box 1)
- Adler, Samuel (SEHNAP), undated (Box 1)
- Adlerblum, Evelyn D. (SEHNAP), undated (Box 1)
- Afferton, Franklin C. III, undated (Box 1)
- Affron, Charles, undated (Box 1)
- Agnen, Hugh E. (STERN), undated (Box 1)
- Agnew, Peter L. (ADMIN - DEC'D.), undated (Box 1)
- Agnon, S.J., undated (Box 2)
- Agnone, Anthony (FAS), undated (Box 2)
- Agovino, Michael, undated (Box 2)
- Agyemang, Osei, undated (Box 2)
- Ahern, Robert F., undated (Box 2)
- Akerman, Chantal, undated (Box 2)
- Aiuto, Thomas Vito, undated (Box 2)
- Akron, Benjamin (LAW), undated (Box 2)
- Al-Askari, Salah A., undated (Box 2)
- Albanis, Gregory, undated (Box 2)
- Alber, Edward, undated (Box 2)
- Alberding, Russell J., undated (Box 2)
- Albert, Marv, undated (Box 2)
- Alcabes, Abraham, undated (Box 2)
- Aldecoa, Dr. Carmen (FAS), undated (Box 2)
- Aldrich, Julian Carter (SEHNAP), undated (Box 2)
- Aldridge, John W. (GASAS), undated (Box 2)
- Alec, Percy (Courant), undated (Box 2)
- Ales, Victor (STERN), undated (Box 2)
- Alexander, Elizabeth, undated (Box 2)
- Alexander, Fritz W., undated (Box 2)
- Alexander, George, undated (Box 2)
- Alexander, Lamar, undated (Box 2)
- Alexander, Peter, undated (Box 2)
- Alexander, Peter (FAS), undated (Box 2)
- Alexander, Rodney, undated (Box 2)
- Alexander, William (orig. Alexander Levy), undated (Box 2)
- Alexandrides, C.G. (FAS), undated (Box 2)
- Alfano, Michael C., undated (Box 2)
- Alfant, Rebecca E., undated (Box 2)
- Alfieri, Rosario P. ('69 q.d), undated (Box 2)
- Alfonsin, Raul, undated (Box 2)
- Alger, Chadwick (FAS), undated (Box 2)
- Alford, Leon Pratt, undated (Box 2)
- Allen, Beverly Sprague, undated (Box 2)
- Allen, Catherine Louis (SENHAP), undated (Box 2)
- Allen, Cornelius B. (STERN-ADMIN), undated (Box 2)
- Allen, Florence E. (LAW), undated (Box 2)
- Allen, Gay Wilson, undated (Box 2)
- Allen, Jessie, undated (Box 2)
- Allen, Jerome, undated (Box 2)
- Allen, John Stuart, undated (Box 2)
- Allen, John E. III (FAS), undated (Box 2)
- Allen, Leon J. (DENTAL), undated (Box 2)
- Allen, Mel, undated (Box 2)
- Allen, Stephen, undated (Box 192, Folder 13)
- Allen, Woody, undated (Box 2)
- Allinger, Helen, undated (Box 2)
- Allen-Dutton, Jordan, undated (Box 2)
- Alloway, Dr. David N., undated (Box 2)
- Alpenfels, Dr. Ethel J. (FAS), undated (Box 3)
- Al-Radi, Selma, undated (Box 3)
- Altchek, Victor, undated (Box 3)
- Altman, Edward, undated (Box 3)
- Altman, Leonard, undated (Box 3)
- Altshuler, Alan A. (WAGNER), undated (Box 3)
- Altszuler, Norman, undated (Box 3)
- Amato, Vincent V., undated (Box 3)
- Amdurer, Stanley, undated (Box 3)
- Amelar, Dr. Richard D., undated (Box 3)
- Amenta, Edwin, undated (Box 3)
- Ames, Peter, undated (Box 3)
- Amihud, Yakov, undated (Box 3)
- Amin, Dr. Joab, undated (Box 3)
- Amler, Melvin, undated (Box 3)
- Amodio, David, undated (Box 3)
- Amsterdam, Anthony G., undated (Box 3)
- Amsterdam, Hon Birdie, undated (Box 3)
- Ancowitz, Nancy, undated (Box 3)
- Anderson, Celia, undated (Box 3)
- Anderson, Dole, undated (Box 3)
- Anderson, Edith, undated (Box 3)
- Anderson, Gary, undated (Box 3)
- Anderson, George, undated (Box 3)
- Anderson, Helene, undated (Box 3)
- Anderson, Rodney, undated (Box 3)
- Anderson, Susan, undated (Box 3)
- Anderson, Thomas J., undated (Box 3)
- Anderson, Totten J., undated (Box 4)
- Anderson, Walter Dr., undated (Box 4)
- Andreotti, Giulio, undated (Box 4)
- Andrews, John W., undated (Box 4)
- Andrews, Max, undated (Box 4)
- Andrew, Lucius, undated (Box 4)
- Angell, Frank, undated (Box 4)
- Angell, Frank J., undated (Box 4)
- Angell, James R., undated (Box 4)
- Angoff, Alan, undated (Box 4)
- Angoff, Charles, undated (Box 4)
- Annenberg, Walter, undated (Box 4)
- Anriquez, Laura Novoa de, undated (Box 4)
- Ansari, Aziz, undated (Box 4)
- Ansheen, Frank, undated (Box 4)
- Anthony, Susan B., undated (Box 4)
- Anthony, Mary, undated (Box 4)
- Antonoff, Stanley J, undated (Box 4)
- Antz, Louise, undated (Box 4)
- Anyon, Jean, undated (Box 4)
- Aoki, Chiye, undated (Box 4)
- Appadurai, Arjun (Goddard Professor), undated (Box 4)
- Appel, Cheri, undated (Box 4)
- Appel, Jack I., undated (Box 4)
- Appelfeld, Aharon, undated (Box 4)
- Appiah, Kwame Anthony, undated (Box 4)
- Applegit, Elmer M., undated (Box 4)
- Appleton, Herbert M. Jr., undated (Box 4)
- Appleton, Jean, undated (Box 4)
- Aquino, Corazon, undated (Box 4)
- Arakelian, Peter, undated (Box 4)
- Archer, Lee, undated (Box 4)
- Archbald, Robert W, undated (Box 4)
- Arden, John, undated (Box 4)
- Arden, Kevin, undated (Box 4)
- Arenson, J.T., undated (Box 4)
- Arendt, Hannah, undated (Box 4)
- Ares, Charles, undated (Box 4)
- Argow, Walter, undated (Box 4)
- Arlen, Harold, undated (Box 4)
- Arlow, Jacob, undated (Box 4)
- Ariav, Gad, undated (Box 4)
- Arli, Raymond, undated (Box 4)
- Arm, Adolph '49 and '60 ED, undated (Box 4)
- Armitage, Norman, undated (Box 4)
- Armsey, James W., undated (Box 4)
- Armstrong, Estelle, undated (Box 4)
- Armstrong, George, undated (Box 5)
- Armstrong, J. Sinclair, undated (Box 5)
- Armstrong, George S. Jr., undated (Box 5)
- Armstrong, John C.'42 E, undated (Box 5)
- Armstrong, William G., undated (Box 5)
- Arndt, Christian O., undated (Box 5)
- Arnoff, Dr. Francis W., undated (Box 5)
- Arnold, Arthur Z., undated (Box 5)
- Arnold, Charles B., undated (Box 5)
- Arnold, Dorothy, undated (Box 5)
- Arnold, Lee, undated (Box 5)
- Arnold, Richard B., undated (Box 5)
- Arnoff, Michael S., undated (Box 5)
- Arone, Frank T., undated (Box 5)
- Aronoff, Frances Webber, undated (Box 5)
- Arons, Dr. Michael, undated (Box 5)
- Aronson, Allan R. '40 M, undated (Box 5)
- Aronson, Dr. Raphael, undated (Box 5)
- Aronson, Dr. Sidney, undated (Box 5)
- Arrowsmith, William, undated (Box 5)
- Ashenfelter, Orley C., undated (Box 5)
- Arter, Rheta, undated (Box 5)
- Arthur, James, undated (Box 5)
- Arthur, Paul, undated (Box 5)
- Arvay, Diane '62 A, undated (Box 5)
- Arum, Robert '53 A, undated (Box 5)
- Asgis, Alfred J (DENTAL), undated (Box 5)
- Ashe, Amelia, undated (Box 5)
- Ashenfelter, Orley C., undated (Box 5)
- Asimon, Stanley '51 W., undated (Box 5)
- Askin, Arnold S., undated (Box 5)
- Assael, Henry, undated (Box 5)
- Aster, Alvin K., undated (Box 5)
- Astor, Brooke, undated (Box 5)
- Astor, Vincent, undated (Box 5)
- Atkin, Dr. J. Myron '48 ED., undated (Box 5)
- Atkins, Willard Earl, undated (Box 5)
- Atkinson, Miles, undated (Box 5)
- Atkinson, Thomas E., undated (Box 6)
- Atlas, David, undated (Box 6)
- Atlas, Martin, undated (Box 6)
- Attinger, Joelle, undated (Box 6)
- Attanasio, Joseph F., undated (Box 6)
- Atyeo, Henry C., undated (Box 6)
- Atzmon, Dr. Exri, undated (Box 6)
- Auchincloss, Louis, undated (Box 6)
- Austin, Jon N., undated (Box 6)
- Auerbach, Ethel O., undated (Box 6)
- Auerbach, Dr. Morris, undated (Box 6)
- Auerbach, Oscar, undated (Box 6)
- Austen, Ralph, undated (Box 6)
- Aufrichtig, Michael, undated (Box 6)
- Austern, H. Thomas '26 WSC, undated (Box 6)
- Axelrod, Herbert R., undated (Box 6)
- Axline, Dr. Virginia, undated (Box 6)
- Axtelle, George E., undated (Box 6)
- Axworthy, H. Harold, undated (Box 6)
- Ayala, Francisco, undated (Box 6)
- Ayars, William Class of 1864, undated (Box 6)
- Ayearst, Morley, undated (Box 6)
- Ayer, Alfred J., undated (Box 6)
- Aygen, Cemal Mahmut, undated (Box 6)
- Azenberg, Emanuel '55 A, undated (Box 6)
- Azmitia, Ephraim, undated (Box 6)
- Azzarelli, Joseph J., undated (Box 6)
- Bart, Stanley, undated (Box 6)
- Babakahnian, Arthur, undated (Box 6)
- Babian, Haig, undated (Box 6)
- Babin, Maria, undated (Box 6)
- Baccus, Stephen, undated (Box 6)
- Bachman, Andrew, undated (Box 6)
- Bachman, Rima, undated (Box 6)
- Bachrach, Max, undated (Box 6)
- Bacic, Zlatko, undated (Box 6)
- Backer, Morton, undated (Box 6)
- Backman, Grace Straim, undated (Box 6)
- Backman, Jules, undated (Box 6)
- Backman, Jules, undated (Box 7)
- Badaracco, Mary Anne, undated (Box 7)
- Baden, Dr. Michael M., undated (Box 7)
- Bader, Louis, undated (Box 7)
- Badger, Philip O., undated (Box 7)
- Badham, John, undated (Box 7)
- Badillo, Herman, undated (Box 7)
- Baer, William Bush, undated (Box 7)
- Baer, Ellen D., undated (Box 7)
- Baer, Norbert, undated (Box 7)
- Baer, Rudolf, undated (Box 7)
- Baer, Rudolf L., undated (Box 7)
- Baez, Silvio M.D., undated (Box 7)
- Bagnall, Roger, undated (Box 7)
- Bahrenburg, D. Claeys, undated (Box 7)
- Bahry, Donna, undated (Box 7)
- Bailey, Bertha, undated (Box 7)
- Bailey, Edward, undated (Box 7)
- Bailey, Robert, undated (Box 7)
- Bailey, G.E., undated (Box 7)
- Bailey, Robert (Political Science), undated (Box 7)
- Bain, Beverly, undated (Box 7)
- Baird, George Hetzel, undated (Box 7)
- Baird, Henry Martyn, undated (Box 7)
- Bakeless, John, undated (Box 7)
- Baker, Annie, undated (Box 7)
- Baker, Cornelius, undated (Box 7)
- Baker, Paul R., undated (Box 8)
- Baker, Elmer E. Jr., undated (Box 8)
- Baker, Fred, undated (Box 8)
- Baker, G. Derwood, undated (Box 8)
- Baker, Harold A., undated (Box 8)
- Baker, James, undated (Box 8)
- Baker, John Tull, undated (Box 8)
- Baker, John H., undated (Box 8)
- Bakht, Natasha, undated (Box 8)
- Bakst, Aaron, undated (Box 8)
- Bakwin, Harry, undated (Box 8)
- Bakwin, Ruth M., undated (Box 8)
- Balaban, Max O. (Dental), undated (Box 8)
- Balagna, John A., undated (Box 8)
- Balakian, Anna, undated (Box 8)
- Balbiani, Andrew S., undated (Box 8)
- Baldwin, Alec, undated (Box 8)
- Baldwin, Dr. Albrid, undated (Box 8)
- Baldwin, Marshall, undated (Box 8)
- Baldwin, Roger N., undated (Box 8)
- Baldwin, W.M., undated (Box 8)
- Bales, W.M., undated (Box 8)
- Balint, Andras, undated (Box 8)
- Ball, Charles E., undated (Box 8)
- Ball, Edith L., undated (Box 8)
- Ball, George W., undated (Box 8)
- Ballantine, Lesley Frost, undated (Box 8)
- Ballantyne, Donald, undated (Box 8)
- Ballenger, Lois T. '49 Ed, undated (Box 8)
- Ballerini, Luigi, undated (Box 8)
- Balliet, Thomas M., undated (Box 8)
- Ballon, Hillary, undated (Box 8)
- Ballow, John N., undated (Box 8)
- Balme, Basil E., undated (Box 8)
- Balter, Lawrence, undated (Box 8)
- Baltzly, Alexander, undated (Box 8)
- Bambrick, James Jr., undated (Box 8)
- Bancroft, Harding Foster, undated (Box 8)
- Bancroft, Sarah, undated (Box 8)
- Bander, Edward J., undated (Box 8)
- Banks, Carol M., undated (Box 8)
- Banks, David, undated (Box 8)
- Banks, Hugh C., undated (Box 8)
- Banks, Lawrence J. '55 C, undated (Box 9)
- Banks, Paul, undated (Box 9)
- Baraka, Amiri, undated (Box 9)
- Barasch, Dr. Frances K., undated (Box 9)
- Barasch, Marvin '47 C, undated (Box 9)
- Barbato, Joseph A., undated (Box 9)
- Barber, Walter "Red", undated (Box 9)
- Barberi, Andrew, undated (Box 9)
- Bardes, Philip, undated (Box 9)
- Barenblatt, Lloyd, undated (Box 9)
- Barfield, Samuel, undated (Box 9)
- Bargh, John A., undated (Box 9)
- Barish, Norman N., undated (Box 9)
- Barkan, Leonard, undated (Box 9)
- Barksdale, Hiram Collier, undated (Box 9)
- Barksdale, James M. '81 W, undated (Box 9)
- Barksdale, W. Lane Dr., undated (Box 9)
- Barlow, Horace B., undated (Box 9)
- Barlow, Joseph, undated (Box 9)
- Barns, Falter, undated (Box 9)
- Barolini, Teodolinda, undated (Box 9)
- Barnard, J. Darrell, undated (Box 9)
- Barnes, Clive, undated (Box 9)
- Barnes, Cyrus W., undated (Box 9)
- Barnes, Harry Elmer, undated (Box 9)
- Barnes, Walter, undated (Box 9)
- Barnett, Dick, undated (Box 9)
- Barnett, James Parker, undated (Box 9)
- Barnett, Michael, undated (Box 9)
- Barnicle, Mary Elizabeth, undated (Box 9)
- Barofsky, Neil M., undated (Box 9)
- Baron, Louis, undated (Box 9)
- Baron, Ned, undated (Box 9)
- Baron, Sydney S., undated (Box 9)
- Baer, Edward E. '57 C, undated (Box 9)
- Barr, Jean B., undated (Box 9)
- Barr, Sherman (SSW), undated (Box 9)
- Barrett, Lawrence I '56 W, undated (Box 9)
- Barrett, Paulette, undated (Box 9)
- Barrett, Richard S., undated (Box 9)
- Barrett, Sampson, undated (Box 9)
- Barrett, Dr. William C., undated (Box 9)
- Barrick, Daniel, undated (Box 10)
- Barrows, David N., undated (Box 10)
- Barry, David, undated (Box 10)
- Barry, Kim, undated (Box 10)
- Barstow, Robbins, undated (Box 10)
- Barta, Andrew, undated (Box 10)
- Bartels, Theodore, R., undated (Box 10)
- Barlett, Craig, undated (Box 10)
- Barth, Ilene, undated (Box 10)
- Bartiromo, Maria, undated (Box 10)
- Bartley, Robert L., undated (Box 10)
- Bartner, Martin, undated (Box 10)
- Bartolomei, Jeanne, undated (Box 10)
- Baruch, Sylvia, undated (Box 10)
- Baskin, Samuel '48 Ed, '54 Ed, undated (Box 10)
- Baskin, Leonard, undated (Box 10)
- Basch, Linda, undated (Box 10)
- Bassine, Charles C., undated (Box 10)
- Basowitz, Harold, undated (Box 10)
- Basu, Jhumki, undated (Box 10)
- Basuscu, Sabert, undated (Box 10)
- Bates, Ralph, undated (Box 10)
- Bates, Len, undated (Box 10)
- Bates, A. Allen, undated (Box 10)
- Bates, Robert, undated (Box 10)
- Batka, Fred, undated (Box 10)
- Battaile, Harry C., undated (Box 10)
- Baudin, Maurice Sr., undated (Box 10)
- Baudin, Maurice Jr., undated (Box 10)
- Bauer-Mengelberg, Stefan, undated (Box 10)
- Bauer, Frances, undated (Box 10)
- Bauer, Marion, undated (Box 10)
- Baughman, George, undated (Box 10)
- Baum, Werner, undated (Box 10)
- Baumbach, Jonathan, undated (Box 10)
- Baumbach, Roger K. '64 GBA, undated (Box 10)
- Baumol, William J., undated (Box 11)
- Baxter, John Clifford, undated (Box 11)
- Bayer, Henry G., undated (Box 11)
- Bazzi, Mohamad, undated (Box 11)
- Be, Genesis, undated (Box 11)
- Beaman, Florence, undated (Box 11)
- Bean, Carolyn, undated (Box 11)
- Beard, Dr. Raymond S., undated (Box 11)
- Bearden, (Howard) Romare, undated (Box 11)
- Bearden, (Howard) Romare, undated (Box 12)
- Beattie, Helen J., undated (Box 12)
- Beatty, Eileen R. '81 C, undated (Box 12)
- Beatty, Vander L., undated (Box 12)
- Beauchamp, Dr. Mary, undated (Box 12)
- Beaumont, Andre, undated (Box 12)
- Beck, Martin, undated (Box 12)
- Beckel, Dr. Graham, undated (Box 12)
- Becker, Frederick F., undated (Box 12)
- Becker, Herbert, undated (Box 12)
- Becker, James F., undated (Box 12)
- Becker, LaFollette '47 W, undated (Box 12)
- Becker, Marilyn J. '50, '54, undated (Box 12)
- Becker, Murray C., undated (Box 12)
- Becker, Richard, undated (Box 12)
- Becker, Reinhard, undated (Box 12)
- Becker, Sandy, undated (Box 12)
- Becker, Stuart '64 C, '73 GBA, undated (Box 12)
- Becker, Theodore, undated (Box 12)
- Becker, Dr. William H. '52 W, '56 M, undated (Box 12)
- Becket, Paul E., undated (Box 13)
- Beckles, Hilary, undated (Box 13)
- Beckman, John, undated (Box 13)
- Bederson, Benjamin, undated (Box 13)
- Bedrosian, Dr. Hrach, undated (Box 13)
- Beechman, Laurie, undated (Box 13)
- Beers, Dr. William, undated (Box 13)
- Beers, Yardley, undated (Box 13)
- Been, Vicki, undated (Box 13)
- Beethhoven, Jane, undated (Box 13)
- Beiser, Arthu, undated (Box 13)
- Begley, Josh, undated (Box 13)
- Begrisch, Frank, undated (Box 13)
- Begun, Martin S., undated (Box 13)
- Behlen, Frieda J., undated (Box 13)
- Beidelman, Thomas, undated (Box 13)
- Beicke, Joan M., undated (Box 13)
- Beishline, Dr. John R., undated (Box 13)
- Beiser, Arthur, undated (Box 13)
- Beitelman, Dr. Martin E. '48 D, undated (Box 13)
- Belafonte, Harry, undated (Box 13)
- Beejack, Barbara, undated (Box 13)
- Belfer, Diane, undated (Box 13)
- Belford, Lee A., undated (Box 13)
- Bell, Alexander Graham, undated (Box 13)
- Bell, Dr. A. Milton '47 W. '51 D, undated (Box 13)
- Bell, Claire N., undated (Box 13)
- Bell, Derrick, undated (Box 13)
- Bell, Kathryn W., undated (Box 13)
- Bell, Samuel Dennis, undated (Box 13)
- Bellak, Leopold, undated (Box 13)
- Bellamy, Carol K., undated (Box 13)
- Belle, Anne, undated (Box 13)
- Bellemore, Douglas H., undated (Box 13)
- Belman, Sidney, undated (Box 14)
- Bellow, Saul, undated (Box 14)
- Belluso, John, undated (Box 14)
- Belmont, Eleanor R., undated (Box 14)
- Belodedova, Irina, undated (Box 14)
- Benabou, Roland Jean-Marc, undated (Box 14)
- Benacerraf, Baruj, undated (Box 14)
- Benardete, Seth, undated (Box 14)
- Benben, John S., undated (Box 14)
- Bender, Lauretta, undated (Box 14)
- Bender, Milton, undated (Box 14)
- Benderson, Bruce, undated (Box 14)
- Bender, Thomas, undated (Box 14)
- Benedek, Laslo, undated (Box 14)
- Benfey, Philip, undated (Box 14)
- Benedetti, Pichler, A.A., undated (Box 14)
- Benenson, Claire, undated (Box 14)
- Benesch, John, undated (Box 14)
- Benhabib, Jess, undated (Box 14)
- Bennet, Ivan L., undated (Box 14)
- Benhaim, Hermine, undated (Box 14)
- Behar, Gabriel, undated (Box 14)
- Benjamin, Jessica, undated (Box 14)
- Benke, Blake, undated (Box 15)
- Benkler, Yochai, undated (Box 15)
- Ben-Muir, Alon, undated (Box 15)
- Bennett-Berg, Arnold, undated (Box 15)
- Bennett, Addison Curtis, undated (Box 15)
- Bennett, James Gordon, undated (Box 15)
- Bennett, Leon, undated (Box 15)
- Benoit, Jean Pierre M., undated (Box 15)
- Benson, Charles E., undated (Box 15)
- Benson, Kenneth R., undated (Box 15)
- Benson, Rodney, undated (Box 15)
- Benz, Margaret Gilbert, undated (Box 15)
- Berchuk, Irving, undated (Box 15)
- Berelson, Irving, undated (Box 15)
- Berenbaum. Rose Levy, undated (Box 15)
- Berenson, Irving M., undated (Box 15)
- Berent, Eherhard F., undated (Box 15)
- Berezin, Evelyn, undated (Box 15)
- Berezin, Irving, undated (Box 15)
- Berg, Irving H. Rev. Dr, undated (Box 15)
- Berg, Morris, undated (Box 15)
- Berg, Thomas, undated (Box 15)
- Berger, Adolph, undated (Box 15)
- Berger, Arthur, undated (Box 15)
- Berger, Bruce, undated (Box 15)
- Bergdoll, Brian, undated (Box 15)
- Berger, Dorothea, undated (Box 15)
- Berger, Eugene, undated (Box 15)
- Berger, Helen, undated (Box 15)
- Berger, Ira, undated (Box 15)
- Berger, H. Jean, undated (Box 15)
- Berger, Milton, undated (Box 15)
- Berger, Morris, undated (Box 15)
- Berger, Marsha, undated (Box 15)
- Berger, Peter L., undated (Box 15)
- Berger, Robert E., undated (Box 15)
- Berger, Stephen, undated (Box 15)
- Bergethon, Bjornar, undated (Box 15)
- Bergh, Louis, undated (Box 15)
- Bergman, Eddie, undated (Box 15)
- Bergmann, Martin S., undated (Box 15)
- Bergmann, Peter G., undated (Box 15)
- Bergreen, John, undated (Box 15)
- Bergreen, Morris, undated (Box 15)
- Berk, Irving A., undated (Box 15)
- Berkman, Dave, undated (Box 15)
- Berkman, Herman G., undated (Box 15)
- Berkeley, William, undated (Box 15)
- Berman, Lillian, undated (Box 15)
- Berkman, Tessie, undated (Box 15)
- Berkowitz, Jerome, undated (Box 15)
- Berkowitz, Pearl N., undated (Box 15)
- Berlant, Kate, undated (Box 15)
- Berlin, Robert S., undated (Box 15)
- Berliner, Howard, undated (Box 15)
- Berliner, Robert W., undated (Box 15)
- Berliner, William, undated (Box 16)
- Berlowitz, Lawrence, undated (Box 16)
- Berlowitz, Leslie, undated (Box 16)
- Berman, Emilez, undated (Box 16)
- Berman, Paul, undated (Box 16)
- Berman, Richard A., undated (Box 16)
- Berman, Simon, undated (Box 16)
- Berman, William 28' D., undated (Box 16)
- Bernard, Claudie, undated (Box 16)
- Bernard, J. Darrell, undated (Box 16)
- Bernard, Viola, undated (Box 16)
- Bernays, Edward, undated (Box 16)
- Bernbach, William '33 C, undated (Box 16)
- Berne, Robert, undated (Box 16)
- Bernecker, Dr. Edward M., undated (Box 16)
- Bernhardt, Debra E., undated (Box 16)
- Bernheimer, Martin '62 G, undated (Box 16)
- Bernie, Robert M., undated (Box 16)
- Berns, Charles A., undated (Box 16)
- Bernstein, Carl, undated (Box 16)
- Bernstein, David, undated (Box 16)
- Bernstein, Elmer, undated (Box 16)
- Bernstein, Irving, undated (Box 16)
- Bernstein, Dr. Isadore, undated (Box 16)
- Bernstein, Jeremy, undated (Box 16)
- Bernstein, Leonard, undated (Box 16)
- Bernstein, Martin L., undated (Box 16)
- Bernstein, Richard S. Esq., '64 L, undated (Box 16)
- Berresford, Susan, undated (Box 16)
- Berrin, Shani, undated (Box 16)